Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers ca. 1954-1992 MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XII: Library, 148277
  - ---. Welcome to the Barbeque. Long Island City: Low-Tech Press, 1990., 148638 (Box XII.20, Folder 389)
  - Kunst Koln. March 1986., 148637 (Box XII.20, Folder 390)
  - Kunstforum. Bd. 76 Nov/Dec 1984., 148636 (Box XII.20, Folder 391)
  - Kunstforum. Bd. 84 Jun. /Jul. /Aug. 1986, 148635 (Box XII.20, Folder 392)
  - LaFarge, Oliver. A Pictorial History of the American Indian. New York: Crown, 1956., 148633 (Box XII.20, Folder 394)
  - Laing, R. D. The Politics of Experience. New York: Ballantine Books, 1967., 148632 (Box XII.20, Folder 395)
  - Lakeland, William, ed. Voices of Achilles: Selected Major Poetry of Arthur Rimbaud. Berkeley: Abracadabra, 1973., 148631 (Box XII.20, Folder 396)
  - The Land and Wildlife of Australia. Alexandria, VI: Time-Life, 1964., 148630 (Box XII.20, Folder 397)
  - Lane, Frank W. The Elements Rage. Philadelphia: Chilton Books, 1965., 148629 (Box XII.20, Folder 398)
  - The Lapis Press. Venice, CA: Lapis Press, n. d., undated; 148628 (Box XII.20, Folder 399)
  - Larson, Gary. The Far Side Gallery. Kansas City: Andrews, McMeel and Parker, 1985., 148627 (Box XII.20, Folder 400)
  - Lauter, Wolfgang. Licht. Dortmund: Harenberg, 1986., 148626 (Box XII.20, Folder 401)
  - Lawrence, D. H. Mornings in Mexico. London: Penguin, 1988., 148625 (Box XII.20, Folder 402)
  - Leonard, C. H. The Concise Gray's Anatomy. Secaucus, NJ: Chartwell Books, 1983., 148624 (Box XII.20, Folder 403)
  - Lesbians, Gay Men and the Law, ed. William B. Rubenstein. New York: The New Press, 1993. Cataloged as part of the Downtown Collection., 148622 (Box XII.20, Folder 404A.)
  - Levi, Herbert W. Spiders and Their Kin. New York: Golden Press, 1987., 148621 (Box XII.20, Folder 405)
  - Levi, Primo. The Mirror Maker. Trans. Raymond Rosenthal. New York: Schocken Books, 1989., 148620 (Box XII.20, Folder 406)
  - Leyda, Jay, ed. and trans. Sergei Eisenstein: Film Form. New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovitch, 1949., 148619 (Box XII.20, Folder 407)
  - Life Saving & Water Safety. The American Red Cross. Washington D. C.: Blakiston Co., 1937., 148618 (Box XII.20, Folder 408)
  - Life Saving & Water Safety. The American Red Cross. Washington D. C.: Blakiston Co., 1956. [inscribed on cover with "Use in Performance" in yellow chalk], 148617 (Box XII.20, Folder 409)
  - Lineaweaver III, Thomas H., and Richard H. Backus. The Natural History of Sharks. New York: Nick Lyons Books, 1970., 148616 (Box XII.20, Folder 410)
  - Link, Howard A. The Art of Masami Teraoka. Honolulu: The Contemporary Museum, 1988., 148615 (Box XII.20, Folder 411)
  - Lippard, Lucy R. Mixed Blessings. New York: Pantheon Books, 1990. [inscribed], 148614 (Box XII.20, Folder 412)
  - Lista, Giovanni. Le Futurisme. Milan: Hazan, 1985., 148613 (Box XII.20, Folder 413)
  - Little Caesar. #11, 198-?, 1980-1989; 148612 (Box XII.21, Folder 414)
  - Livingston, Jane and John Beardsley. Black Folk Art in America 1930-1980. Jackson: UP of Mississippi, 1982., 148611 (Box XII.21, Folder 415)
  - Lobsenz,, Norman M. The Insect World. New York: Golden Press, 1959., 148610 (Box XII.21, Folder 416)
  - Local: An Anthology of the Subway Experience. New York: Zone Press, 1977., 148609 (Box XII.21, Folder 416A.)
  - Lockhart, R. D. Living Anatomy: A Photographic Atlas of Muscles in Action and Surface Contours. London: Faber and Faber, 1970., 148608 (Box XII.21, Folder 417)
  - Lommel, Andreas. Masks. New York: Excalibur Books, 1970., 148607 (Box XII.21, Folder 418)
  - London, Jack. The Road. Santa Barbara: Peregrine Smith, 1978., 148606 (Box XII.21, Folder 419)
  - Lopez, Nacho. La Ciudad de Mexico III. Mexico: Artes de Mexico, Nov/Dec 1964., 148605 (Box XII.21, Folder 420)
  - Los Angeles Festival Program. [n. p. ] 1990., 148604 (Box XII.21, Folder 421)
  - Lucha Libre. 2 Nov. 1986, 148603 (Box XII.21, Folder 422)
  - Luis Cruz Azaceta. Koln: Kunst-Station, 1988., 148602 (Box XII.21, Folder 423)
  - Lumsden, E. S. The Art of Etching. New York: Dover Publications, 1962., 148601 (Box XII.21, Folder 424)
  - Lupu, Francois. Oceanie le Masque au Long Cours. Rennes: Ouest France, 1983., 148600 (Box XII.21, Folder 425)
  - Lykiard, Alexis, trans. Lautreamont's Maldoror. New York: Thomas Y. Crowell Company, 1972., 148599 (Box XII.21, Folder 426)
  - Lyon, Danny. Conversations with the Dead. New York: Holt, Rinehart and Winston, 1971, 148598 (Box XII.21, Folder 427)
  - ---. Merci Gonaives. New York: Bleak Beauty, 1988., 148597 (Box XII.21, Folder 428)
  - ---. The Paper Negative. Bernalillo, NM: Bleak Beauty, 1980., 148596 (Box XII.21, Folder 429)
  - ---. Pictures from the New World. New York: Aperture, 1981., 148595 (Box XII.21, Folder 430)
  - Lyotard, Jean-Francois. Driftworks. New York: Semiotext(e), 1984., 148594 (Box XII.21, Folder 431)
  - MacKinnon, John. Borneo. Amsterdam: Time-Life, 1975., 148593 (Box XII.21, Folder 432)
  - Madigan, Kip. Rene. Fresno, CA: Fabian Books, 1955., 148592 (Box XII.21, Folder 433)
  - Maeterlinck, Maurice. La Vie des Termites/La Vie des Fournis. Geneve: Editions Famot, 1977., 148591 (Box XII.21, Folder 434)
  - Mahuzier, Albert. Grandes Chasses en Afrique Centrale. Paris: Amiot-Dumont, 1947., 148590 (Box XII.21, Folder 435)
  - Malcolm Morley. London: Whitechapel Art Gallery, 1983., 148589 (Box XII.22, Folder 436)
  - Malcolm Morley. New York: Xavier Fourcade, 1986., 148588 (Box XII.22, Folder 437)
  - Malcolm Morley. New York: Pace Prints, 1987., 148587 (Box XII.22, Folder 438)
  - Maloney, William E. The Great Disasters. New York: Grosset & Dunlap, 1976., 148586 (Box XII.22, Folder 439)
  - Malraux, Andre, ed. Grece Classique. Paris: Gallimard, 1969., 148585 (Box XII.22, Folder 440)
  - Mandate. Vol. 13, No. 6 June 1989., 148584 (Box XII.22, Folder 441)
  - Mann, Thomas. Death in Venice. Trans. H. T. Lowe-Porter. London: Penguin, 1971., 148583 (Box XII.22, Folder 442)
  - Marcel Duchamp: A Retrospective Exhibition Philadelphia: Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1973., 148582 (Box XII.22, Folder 443)
  - Maresca, Frank and Roger Ricco. Bill Traylor. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1991., 148581 (Box XII.22, Folder 444)
  - Mark Innerst: Landscape and Beyond. Normal: Illinois State University, 1988., 148580 (Box XII.22, Folder 445)
  - Marko, Ksynia. Embroidery. London: Octopus, 1982., 148579 (Box XII.22, Folder 446)
  - Marks, C. W.; Ed. Collection de Potpourris des Meilleurs Operas. Hambourg: Aug. Cranz, [n. d. ]. [source material], undated; 148578 (Box XII.22, Folder 447)
  - Marshall, John. Rail: Guinness Factbook. London: Guinness Books, 1985., 148577 (Box XII.22, Folder 448)
  - Martin, Rupert, ed. The View from Above: 125 Years of Aerial Photography. London: The Photographers' Gallery, 1983., 148576 (Box XII.22, Folder 449)
  - Mathers, Michael. Riding the Rails. Boston: Houghton Mifflin, 1974., 148575 (Box XII.22, Folder 450)
  - Matthiessen, Peter. The Cloud Forest. New York: Penguin, 1987., 148574 (Box XII.22, Folder 451)
  - ---. The Snow Leopard. New York: Penguin, 1987., 148573 (Box XII.22, Folder 452)
  - The Mayas. Mexico: GV Editores, 1985., 148572 (Box XII.22, Folder 453)
  - McCarthy, Cormac. Blood Meridian. New York: Ecco Press, 1988., 148571 (Box XII.22, Folder 454)
  - McCormick, Ken and Hamilton Darby Perry. Images of War. New York: Orion Books, 1990./ McGuire, Thomas, DDS. The Tooth Trip: An Oral Experience. New York: Random House, 1972., 148570 (Box XII.22, Folder 455)
  - McKibben, Bill. The End of Nature. New York: Random House, 1989., 148569 (Box XII.22, Folder 456)
  - McMillan, Terry. Disappearing Acts. New York: Washington Square Press, 1990., 148568 (Box XII.23, Folder 457)
  - Medical Infrared Photography. New York: Eastman Kodak, 1973., 148567 (Box XII.23, Folder 458)
  - The Medici Aesop. Trans. Bernard McTigue. New York: Harry N. Abrams, 1989., 148566 (Box XII.23, Folder 459)
  - Meinkoth, Norman A. The Audubon Society Field Guide to North American Seashore Creatures. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1981., 148565 (Box XII.23, Folder 460)
  - Meiselas, Susan. Nicaragua. New York: Pantheon Books, 1981., 148564 (Box XII.23, Folder 461)
  - Meletzis, Spyros, and Helen Papdakis. Archaologisches Nationalmusem Athen. Munchen: Verlag Schnell & Steiner, 1977., 148563 (Box XII.23, Folder 462)
  - Menen, Aubrey. Cities in the Sand. New York: The Dial Press, 1973., 148562 (Box XII.23, Folder 463)
  - Meyer, Franz Sales. Handbook of Ornament. New York: Dover Publications, 1957., 148561 (Box XII.23, Folder 464)
  - Meyer, Karl E. Teotihuacan. New York: Newsweek, 1973., 148560 (Box XII.23, Folder 465)
  - Michals, Duane. Homage to Cavafy. Danbury, NH: Addison House, 1978., 148559 (Box XII.23, Folder 466)
  - Michaux, Henri. Selected Writings. Trans. Richard Ellman. New York: New Directions, 1968., 148558 (Box XII.23, Folder 467)
  - Miller, John and David Pelham. The Facts of Life. New York: Viking, 1984., 148557 (Box XII.23, Folder 468)
  - Milne, Lorus and Margery. The Audubon Society Field Guide to North American Insects and Spiders. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1988., 148556 (Box XII.23, Folder 469)
  - Mishima, Yukio. Confessions of a Mask. New York: New Directions, 1958., 148555 (Box XII.23, Folder 470)
  - ---. The Sea of Fertility: Spring Snow. Trans. Michael Gallagher. Vol. 1 New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1973., 148554 (Box XII.23, Folder 471)
  - ---. The Sea of Fertility: Runaway Horses. Trans. Michael Gallagher. Vol. 2 New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1973., 148553 (Box XII.24, Folder 472)
  - ---. The Sea of Fertility: The Temple of Dawn. Trans. Michael Gallagher. Vol. 3 New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1973., 148552 (Box XII.24, Folder 473)
  - ---. The Sea of Fertility: The Decay of the Angel. Trans. Michael Gallagher. Vol. 4 New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1973., 148551 (Box XII.24, Folder 474)
  - Mitchner, Stuart. Indian Action: An American Journey to the Great Fair of the East. Boston: Little, Brown and Company, 1976., 148550 (Box XII.24, Folder 475)
  - Moir, Alfred. Caravaggio. New York: Harry N. Abrams, 1989., 148549 (Box XII.24, Folder 476)
  - Momento Mori. [n. p. ]: Centro Cultural/Arte Contemporaneo, 1986., 148548 (Box XII.24, Folder 477)
  - Monette, Paul. Becoming a Man. New York: HBJ, 1992., 148547 (Box XII.24, Folder 478)
  - Moon, Dolly M. My Very First Book of Cowboy Songs. New York: Dover, 1982., 148546 (Box XII.24, Folder 479)
  - Moore, Keith L. The Developing Human. Philadelphia: W. B Saunders Co., 1977., 148545 (Box XII.24, Folder 480)
  - Morales, Demetrio Sodi. The Maya World. Mexico: Minutiae Mexicana, 1976., 148544 (Box XII.24, Folder 481)
  - Morris, Jan. Journeys. New York: Oxford University Press, 1984., 148543 (Box XII.24, Folder 482)
  - Mortuary Posts of the Giryama. New York: Friends of Bronx Community Art Gallery, April 28-May 20, 1978., 148542 (Box XII.24, Folder 483)
  - Motor Auto Repair Manual. Second Vintage Car Edition, 1953-61. New York: Motor, 1981., 148541 (Box XII.24, Folder 484)
  - Mrabet, Mohammed. Marriage with Papers. Trans. Paul Bowles. Bolinas, CA: Tombouctou Books, 1986., 148540 (Box XII.24, Folder 485)
  - Mueller, Cookie. Walking Through Clear Water in a Pool Painted Black. New York: Semiotext(e), 1990., 148539 (Box XII.24, Folder 486)
  - Muench, David, and Donald D. Pike. Anasazi: Ancient People of the Rock. Palo Alto, CA: America West Publishing Co., 1974., 148538 (Box XII.25, Folder 487)
  - Muktananda, Swami. Does Death Really Exist? South Fallsburg, NY: SYDA Foundation, 1981., 148537 (Box XII.25, Folder 488)
  - ---. I Have Become Alive. South Fallsburg, NY: SYDA Foundation, 1985., 148536 (Box XII.25, Folder 489)
  - ---. Kundalini: The Secret of Life. South Fallsburg, NY: SYDA Foundation, 1979., 148535 (Box XII.25, Folder 490)
  - ---. Meditate. Albany: State University of New York Press, 1980., 148534 (Box XII.25, Folder 491)
  - Municipal Index and Atlas. New York: American City Magazine Corporation, 1940., 148533 (Box XII.25, Folder 492)
  - ---. New York: American City Magazine Corporation,1941., 148532 (Box XII.25, Folder 493)
  - The Nation. 13 Feb. 1989, 148531 (Box XII.25, Folder 494)
  - ---. 20 Mar. 1989, 148530 (Box XII.25, Folder 495)
  - The National Enquirer. 31 July 1990., 148529 (Box XII.25, Folder 496)
  - National Geographic [cover altered]. Vol. 154, No. 4 October 1978., 148528 (Box XII.25, Folder 497)
  - National and International Studio Programs 1983-1984: P. S. 1, The Clocktower. New York: Institute for Art and Urban Resources, 1984., 148526 (Box XII.25, Folder 499)
  - National Museum of Anthropology, Mexico. Mexico: GV Editores, 1986., 148525 (Box XII.25, Folder 500)
  - Neese, Robert. Prison Exposures. Philadelphia: Chilton Company Book Division, 1959., 148524 (Box XII.25, Folder 501)
  - Neo York: Report on a Phenomenon. Santa Barbara, CA: University Art Museum, 1984., 148523 (Box XII.25, Folder 502)
  - Neruda, Pablo. A New Decade Poems 1958-1967. Trans. Ben Belitt and Alastair Reid. New York: Grove, 1969., 148522 (Box XII.25, Folder 503)
  - ---. New Poems. Trans. and Ed. Ben Belitt. New York: Grove, 1972. [Pages 6 and 22 marked], 148521 (Box XII.25, Folder 504)
  - New Art Examiner. Nov. 1990, 148520 (Box XII.25, Folder 505)
  - New Narrative Painting: Selections from the Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York. Fort Lauderdale, FL: Museum of Art, 1984., 148519 (Box XII.25, Folder 506)
  - The New Press Catalogue. New York: W. W. Norton & Co., 1992., 148518 (Box XII.25, Folder 507)
  - Newsweek. 11 Mar 1985., 148517 (Box XII.25, Folder 508)
  - The New Wonder World Encyclopedia. Vol. 2. New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957., 148516 (Box XII.25, Folder 509)
  - ---. Vol. 3 New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957., 148515 (Box XII.25, Folder 510)
  - ---. Vol. 4 New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957., 148514 (Box XII.25, Folder 511)
  - ---. Vol. 6 New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957., 148513 (Box XII.26, Folder 512)
  - ---. Vol. 10 New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957., 148512 (Box XII.26, Folder 513)
  - New Year! New Talent! Celebrating Emerging Artists of the Eighties. (advertising supplement), 148511 (Box XII.26, Folder 514)
  - New York. November 5, 1984., 148510 (Box XII.26, Folder 515)
  - ---. June 22, 1987., 148509 (Box XII.26, Folder 516)
  - Nietzsche, Friedrich. Beyond Good and Evil. Trans. Walter Kaufmann. New York: Vintage Books/Random House, 1966., 148490 (Box XII.26, Folder 535)
  - Nilsson, Lennart. Close to Nature. New York: Pantheon, 1984., 148489 (Box XII.26, Folder 536)
  - O'Connor, Flannery. The Complete Stories. New York: Farrar, Straus and Giroux, 1971., 148488 (Box XII.26, Folder 537)
  - O'Hara, Frank. Second Avenue. New York: Totem Press/Corinth Books, 1960., 148487 (Box XII.26, Folder 538)
  - October. No. 43 Winter 1987., 148485 (Box XII.26, Folder 540)
  - Oe, Kenzaburo. Teach Us to Outgrow Our Madness. Trans. John Nathan. New York: Grove Press, 1977., 148484 (Box XII.26, Folder 541)
  - The Old Reliable Catalogue. Aug. 1990, 148483 (Box XII.26, Folder 542)
  - Organizaciechint. No. 229 Abril/Mayo/Junio. 1983, 148482 (Box XII.26, Folder 543)
  - Our Amazing World of Nature. Pleasantville, NY: Reader's Digest Association, 1969. [pages 25, 40, 46, 85, 131, 164-5, 199, 203, 207, 231, 265, 284-5, 302], 148481 (Box XII.26, Folder 544)
  - Outweek. No. 63 12 Sept. 1990, 148479 (Box XII.26, Folder 546)
  - Outwrite '91. [n. p. ] 1991., 148478 (Box XII.26, Folder 547)
  - Owen, Gale R. Rites and Religions of the Anglo-Saxons. New York?: Dorset Press, 1985., 148477 (Box XII.26, Folder 548)
  - Pacific Film Archive. Nov. /Dec. 1992, 148476 (Box XII.26, Folder 549)
  - Painting and Sculpture Today 1986. Indianapolis: Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1986., 148475 (Box XII.26, Folder 550)
  - Palmer, William M. Poisonous Snakes of North Carolina. Raleigh: State Museum of Natural History, 1974., 148474 (Box XII.26, Folder 551)
  - Panizza, Oskar. The Council of Love: A Celestial Tragedy in Five Acts. Trans. Oreste F. Pucciani. New York: Viking Press, 1973., 148473 (Box XII.26, Folder 552)
  - Paretsky, Sara. Killing Orders. New York: Ballantine, 1985., 148471 (Box XII.26, Folder 554)
  - Parkett. No. 21 1989, 148470 (Box XII.27, Folder 555)
  - ---. No. 27 1991, 148469 (Box XII.27, Folder 556)
  - ---. No. 31 1992, 148468 (Box XII.27, Folder 557)
  - Parkhurst, Violet. Painting Sunsets. Tustin, CA: Walter Foster, 1985. (two copies), 148467 (Box XII.27, Folder 558)
  - Pasolini, Pier Paolo. The Divine Mimesis. Trans. Thomas Erling Peterson. Berkeley: Double Dance Press, 1980., 148466 (Box XII.27, Folder 559)
  - ---. The Ragazzi. Trans. Emile Capouya. Manchester: Carcanet, 1986., 148465 (Box XII.27, Folder 560)
  - ---. Roman Nights. Trans. John Shepley. Marlboro, Vt: Marlboro Press, 1986., 148464 (Box XII.27, Folder 561)
  - ---. Roman Poems. Trans. Lawrence Ferlinghetti and Francesca Valente. San Francisco: City Lights, 1986., 148463 (Box XII.27, Folder 562)
  - ---. The Scent of India. Trans. David Price. London: Olive Press, 1984., 148462 (Box XII.27, Folder 563)
  - Patch, Edith M. and Harrison E. Howe. Science at Home. New York: MacMillan, 1937., 148461 (Box XII.27, Folder 564)
  - Pato Donald. 21 Apr. 1987, 148460 (Box XII.27, Folder 565)
  - Pauline's. New York: Pauline Bernatchez, 1991., 148459 (Box XII.27, Folder 566)
  - Pelton, Robert W. and Karen W. Carden. Snake Handlers. Nashville: Thomas Nelson Inc., 1974., 148458 (Box XII.27, Folder 567)
  - Perceptions: Black and White. Frances Wolfson Art Gallery. 1986, 148457 (Box XII.27, Folder 568)
  - Photography Annual. Photography Magazine. 1954, 148456 (Box XII.27, Folder 569)
  - Physique-Art. New York: Roto Color Corp., [n. d. ]., undated; 148455 (Box XII.27, Folder 570)
  - Pickwell, Gayle. Weather. Los Angeles: The Junior Literary Guild, 1937., 148454 (Box XII.27, Folder 571)
  - Piero Manzoni. New York: Hirschl & Adler Modern, 1990., 148453 (Box XII.27, Folder 572)
  - Pittsburgh Center for the Arts. Fall 1983., 148451 (Box XII.27, Folder 574)
  - Platt, Rutherford et. al. Secrets of Life: A True-Life Adventure. New York: Simon and Schuster, 1957., 148450 (Box XII.27, Folder 575)
  - Playguy. Vol. 3, No. 12, undated; 148449 (Box XII.27, Folder 576)
  - Polysexuality. Vol. IV. No. 1 Semiotext(e), 1981., 148448 (Box XII.27, Folder 577)
  - Pomerans, Arnold J., trans. A Small Yes and a Big No: The Autobiography of George Grosz. Feltham, UK: Hamlyn Publishing, 1982., 148447 (Box XII.27, Folder 578)
  - Pop, Iggy. I Need More. New York: Karz-Cohl Publishing, 1982., 148446 (Box XII.27, Folder 579)
  - Popol Vuh. Trans. Ralph Nelson. Boston: Houghton-Mifflin, 1975., 148445 (Box XII.27, Folder 580)
  - Portis, Charles. Norwood. New York: Vintage/Random House, 1985., 148444 (Box XII.28, Folder 581)
  - Powell, William F. How to Paint Clouds and Skyscapes. Tustin, CA: Foster Art Service, 1987., 148443 (Box XII.28, Folder 582)
  - ---. How to Paint Clouds and Skyscapes. Tustin, CA: Foster Art Service, 1989., 148442 (Box XII.28, Folder 583)
  - Pox. No. 61 [n. p. ], [n. d. ]., undated; 148441 (Box XII.28, Folder 584)
  - Preston-Mafham, Rod and Ken. Spiders of the World. New York: Facts on File Publications, 1984., 148440 (Box XII.28, Folder 585)
  - Prignitz-Poda, Helga; ed. Frida Kahlo. Frankfurt: Neue Kritik, 1988., 148439 (Box XII.28, Folder 586)
  - Pringle, Laurence. Dinosaurs and Their World. San Diego: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1968. [Note page 35], 148438 (Box XII.28, Folder 587)
  - Purdy, James. Cabot Wright Begins. New York: Farrar, Straus & Giroux, 1964., 148436 (Box XII.28, Folder 589)
  - PWA Coalition Newsline. Issue #57. Jul. /Aug. 1990, 148435 (Box XII.28, Folder 590)
  - ---. Issue #60. Nov. 1990, 148434 (Box XII.28, Folder 591)
  - QW. No. 44 6 Sept. 1992, 148433 (Box XII.28, Folder 592)
  - Rader, Dotson. I Ain't Marchin' Anymore. New York: Paperback Library, 1964., 148432 (Box XII.28, Folder 593)
  - Rand, Ayn. The Fountainhead. New York: Signet, 1971., 148431 (Box XII.28, Folder 594)
  - Rechy, John. City of Night. New York: Grove Press, 1963., 148429 (Box XII.28, Folder 596)
  - Redrum Magazine: The World of Archie. [n. d. ]; Redrum: The Time of the Assassins [n. d. ]; Redrum: The Charter Arms [n. d. ]., undated; 148428 (Box XII.28, Folder 597)
  - Redtape. #4. Fall-Winter 1983-4., 1983-1984; 148427 (Box XII.28, Folder 598)
  - Rees, Paul K., Fred W. Sparks and Charles Sparks Rees. Algebra, Trigonometry and Analytic Geometry. New York: McGraw-Hill, 1967., 148426 (Box XII.28, Folder 599)
  - Re/Search: William S. Burroughs, Throbbing Gristle, Brion Gysin. San Francisco: Re/Search, 1982., 148425 (Box XII.28, Folder 600)
  - Resnick, Robert and David Halliday. Physics. New York: John Wiley, 1966., 148424 (Box XII.28, Folder 601)
  - Rey Rosa, Rodrigo. The Beggar's Knife. Trans. Paul Bowles. San Francisco: City Lights, 1985. [page 80 marked], 148423 (Box XII.28, Folder 602)
  - Richter, G. M. A. A Handbook of Greek Art. New York: Phaidon Publishers, 1960., 148422 (Box XII.29, Folder 603)
  - Rimbaud, Arthur. Illuminations and Other Prose Poems. Trans. Louise Varese. New York: New Directions/James Laughlin, 1957., 148421 (Box XII.29, Folder 604)
  - Ringgold, Gene and DeWitt Bodeen. The Films of Cecil B. DeMille. New York: The Citadel Press, 1969., 148420 (Box XII.29, Folder 605)
  - Ritter, Bruce. Sometimes God has a Kid's Face. New York: Covenant House, 1988., 148419 (Box XII.29, Folder 606)
  - Riverrun. s. l.: 1975., 148418 (Box XII.29, Folder 606A.)
  - Robert Frank. Boston: Little, Brown and Co., 1986., 148417 (Box XII.29, Folder 607)
  - Rodriguez, Arturo. Mitos en blanco y negro. Madrid: Coleccion arte original, 1979., 148416 (Box XII.29, Folder 608)
  - Rolling Stone. Issue 605. 30 May 1991., 1959; 148415 (Box XII.29, Folder 609)
  - The Rolling Stone Interviews. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1989., 148414 (Box XII.29, Folder 610)
  - Rose, Joel and Catherine Texier; Eds. Between C & D. New York: Penguin, 1988., 148413 (Box XII.29, Folder 611)
  - Rosenfeld, Charles, and Robert Cooke. Earthfire: The Eruption of Mount St. Helens. Cambridge, MA: MIT Press, 1982., 148412 (Box XII.29, Folder 612)
  - Rosenthal, Mark. Anselm Kiefer. Chicago: Art Institute of Chicago, 1987., 148411 (Box XII.29, Folder 613)
  - Sackheim, Eric, ed. The Blues Line: A Collection of Blues Lyrics. New York: Grossman Publishers, 1969., 148410 (Box XII.29, Folder 614)
  - Sagan, Carl, and Ann Druyan. Comet. New York: Random House, 1985., 148409 (Box XII.29, Folder 615)
  - Saint, Assoto; ed. The Road Before Us. New York: Galiens Press, 1991., 148408 (Box XII.29, Folder 616)
  - Saint sstien dans l'histoire de l'art depuis le xv sie. Paris: Jacques Damase Editeur, 1979., 148407 (Box XII.29, Folder 617)
  - Samuels, Peggy and Harold. Contemporary Western Artists. New York: Bonanza Books, 1982., 148406 (Box XII.30, Folder 618)
  - San Francisco Review of Books. Vol. 16, No. 1 Summer 1991., 148405 (Box XII.30, Folder 619)
  - Scavullo, Francesco. Men. New York: Random House, 1977., 148404 (Box XII.30, Folder 620)
  - Schidor, Dieter, and Michael McLernon, eds. Rainer Werner Fassbinder: Querelle, the Film Book. Munchen: Schirmer/Mosel Verlag, 1982., 148403 (Box XII.30, Folder 621)
  - Scholder, Amy and Ira Silverberg; Eds. High Risk. New York: Penguin, 1991., 148402 (Box XII.30, Folder 622)
  - Schulz, Bruno. Sanatorium under the Sign of the Hourglass. Trans. Celina Wieniewska. New York: Penguin, 1979., 148401 (Box XII.30, Folder 623)
  - ---. The Street of Crocodiles. New York: Penguin, 1963., 148400 (Box XII.30, Folder 624)
  - Schwab, Gustav. Gods and Heroes: Myths and Epics of Ancient Greece. New York: Pantheon, 1974., 148399 (Box XII.30, Folder 625)
  - Schwartz, Eugene M. The Sound of One Mind Thinking. San Francisco: Strawberry Hill Press, 1981., 148398 (Box XII.30, Folder 626)